// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It is the process of interactively searching given words/terms to gather specific information.",
    answer: "d. Online Exploration",
    options: [
      "a. Online Mission",
      "b. Online Navigation",
      "c. Online Expedition",
      "d. Online Exploration"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "It is the most known and most used search engine.",
    answer: "c. Google",
    options: [
      "a. Baidu",
      "b. Yahoo",
      "c. Google",
      "d. Ask.com"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Arrange the commands in the correct order when doing a contextualized online navigation:",
    answer: "c. I, II, IV, III",
    options: [
      "a. I, II, III, IV",
      "b. I, III, IV, II",
      "c. I, II, IV, III",
      "d. I, IV, III, II"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "This term refers to the type of information that is relatively considered as fake, untrue, and merely opinion-based.",
    answer: "a. Spoof",
    options: [
      "a. Spoof",
      "b. Satirical",
      "c. Sardonic",
      "d. Sarcastic"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following cannot be considered as a guide in identifying the good source from the satirical source of information?",
    answer: "d. Click any sites that appeared as a source of information",
    options: [
      "a. Check if the site is alleged as satirical",
      "b. Ask someone knowledgeable and get to know the site",
      "c. Always be cautious and read the contents of the source",
      "d. Click any sites that appeared as a source of information"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "These are Software Systems designed to search information on the World Wide Web.",
    answer: "c. Search Engine",
    options: [
      "a. Search Bar",
      "b. Search Tool",
      "c. Search Engine",
      "d. Search Application"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The skill refers to the ability to produce good and continuous searches.",
    answer: "c. Research Skill",
    options: [
      "a. Thinking Skill",
      "b. Learning Skill",
      "c. Research Skill",
      "d. Production Skill"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "This is collectively organizing gathered data and ensuring tracking of specific information.",
    answer: "b. Data Organizing",
    options: [
      "a. Critical Thinking",
      "b. Data Organizing",
      "c. Research Presenting",
      "d. None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A skill that involves the ability to reflect and analyze on the information presented.",
    answer: "a. Critical Thinking",
    options: [
      "a. Critical Thinking",
      "b. Data Organizing",
      "c. Research Presenting",
      "d. None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "This type of skill refers to the ability to express the information through creative writing.",
    answer: "c. Research Presenting",
    options: [
      "a. Critical Thinking",
      "b. Data Organizing",
      "c. Research Presenting",
      "d. None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of the following can be considered as fake, untrue, and merely opinion-based?",
    answer: "d. Dr. Jose Rizal was born on the 19th day of June, not on 30th day of December.",
    options: [
      "a. Dr. Jose Rizal was the Philippinesâ€™ National Hero.",
      "b. Dr. Jose Rizal studied at Ateneo De Manila and University of the Philippines.",
      "c. Dr. Jose Rizal wrote a third book after Noli Me Tangere and El Filibusterismo.",
      "d. Dr. Jose Rizal was born on the 19th day of June, not on 30th day of December."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which of the following information can be considered as a true one?",
    answer: "a. The 15th president of the Republic of the Philippines was Fidel Ramos.",
    options: [
      "a. The 15th president of the Republic of the Philippines was Fidel Ramos.",
      "b. The 15th president of the Republic of the Philippines was Gloria Arroyo.",
      "c. The 15th president of the Republic of the Philippines was Joseph Estrada.",
      "d. The 15th president of the Republic of the Philippines was Benigno Aquino III."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What do you think is the main reason why we online navigate?",
    answer: "c. To be more precise on the information.",
    options: [
      "a. To be more technology-based.",
      "b. To be more comfortable searching.",
      "c. To be more precise on the information.",
      "d. To be more dependent on the internet."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "As a student, how can you apply your understanding on satirical news upon searching?",
    answer: "d. All of the above.",
    options: [
      "a. Read and search.",
      "b. Being observant.",
      "c. Think before you click.",
      "d. All of the above."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "As a student, you are responsible when a specific information was presented to you. Which of these cannot be done upon searching?",
    answer: "c. Click any sites that appeared as a source of information",
    options: [
      "a. Ask someone knowledgeable and get to know the site.",
      "b. Always be cautious and read the contents of the source.",
      "c. Click any sites that appeared as a source of information.",
      "d. Navigate around the internet, and check if the site is alleged as satirical."
    ]
  },
];
